Finding Aid for the Collection of California Postcards LSC.1351
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of California postcards
circa 1890
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.1351
1 unknown (22 oversize boxes)
There were few areas or events not recorded on postcards by the early 1900s. Although their popularity dropped off after World War I, tourist view cards became the standard after World War II. The collection consists of postcards of various places throughout California.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
PORTIONS OF THIS COLLECTION HAVE BEEN DIGITIZED. See the Existence and Location of Copies note for the link to the digitized materials.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digitized materials are available electronically at https://digital.library.ucla.edu/catalog/37sh8000zz-89112.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942327163606533
Scope and Content
The first postcards were probably playing cards used as visiting cards (late 17th-early 18th century); they were replaced by visiting cards and most had pictures and a blank space for the name; subjects were places of interest or general motifs and often included messages; printers printed decorative letter paper using old visiting card plates (1830s) and established the link from visiting cards to postcards; there were few areas or events not recorded on postcards by the early 1900s; popularity dropped off after WWI; tourist view cards became the standard after WWII.
Postcards -- California.; Postcards.
- Agriculture / "California bounty"
  - Agriculture / "California bounty" (Box 5)
- Alhambra
  - Alhambra (Box 5)
- Altadena
  - Altadena (Box 5)
- Amboy
  - Amboy (Box 5)
- Anacapa Islands
  - Anacapa Islands (Box 5)
- Anaheim
  - Anaheim (Box 5)
- Animals
  - Animals (Box 5)
- Antelope Valley
  - Antelope Valley (Box 5)
- Arcadia
  - Arcadia (Box 20)
  - Arcadia: Lucky Baldwin Ranch (Box 5)
  - Arcadia: Pony Express Museum (Box 5)
- Arrowhead
  - Arrowhead (Box 5)
- Azusa
  - Azusa (Box 5)
- Bakersfield
  - Bakersfield (Box 5)
  - Bakersfield (Box 22)
  - Bakersfield: Oil fields (Box 22)
- Balboa
  - Balboa (Box 5)
- Banning
  - Banning (Box 5)
- Barstow
  - Barstow (Box 5)
- Beach scenes
  - Beach scenes (Box 5)
- Bel Air
  - Bel Air (Box 5)
- Beverly Hills
  - Beverly Hills (Box 5)
  - Beverly Hills: Beverly Hills Hotel (Box 5)
- Big Bear Lake
  - Big Bear Lake (Box 5)
- Big Pines Recreation Camp (Los Angeles County)
  - Big Pines Recreation Camp (Los Angeles County) (Box 5)
- Big Sur and Highway 1
  - Big Sur and Highway 1 (Box 20)
- Blythe
  - Blythe (Box 5)
- Borrego Springs
  - Borrego Springs (Box 5)
- Buellton
  - Buellton (Box 5)
- Burbank
  - Burbank (Box 5)
- Cajon Pass
  - Cajon Pass (Box 5)
- California in Midwinter
  - California in Midwinter (Box 5)
- California postcard album - 2 volumes
  - California postcard album - 2 volumes: Vol. 1 - Southern Calif., Vol. 2 - Northern Calif. (Box 21)
- Carpinteria
  - Carpinteria (Box 5)
- Casa Verdugo
  - Casa Verdugo (Box 5)
- Cathedral City
  - Cathedral City (Box 5)
- Central California
  - Central California (Box 20)
- Chatsworth
  - Chatsworth (Box 5)
- Chula Vista
  - Chula Vista (Box 5)
- Claremont
  - Claremont (Box 5)
- Coachella Valley
  - Coachella Valley (Box 5)
- Coast Highway
  - Coast Highway (Box 5)
- Colton
  - Colton (Box 5)
- Compton
  - Compton: Earthquake 1933 (Box 5)
- Corona
  - Corona (Box 5)
- Coronado
  - Coronado (Box 20)
  - Coronado (Box 22)
- Coronado Beach
  - Coronado Beach (Box 5)
- Crestline
  - Crestline (Box 5)
- Cucamonga Mountain
  - Cucamonga Mountain (Box 5)
- Culver City
  - Culver City (Box 5)
- Death Valley
  - Death Valley (Box 5)
- Del Mar
  - Del Mar (Box 5)
- Desert scenes
  - Desert scenes (Box 5)
  - Desert scenes: [Box 20 is an oversize flat box] (Box 20)
- Disneyland
  - Disneyland (Box 5)
- Eagle Rock
  - Eagle Rock (Box 5)
- El Centro
  - El Centro (Box 5)
- El Molino Canyon
  - El Molino Canyon (Box 5)
- El Monte
  - El Monte (Box 5)
- Escondido
  - Escondido (Box 5)
- Fallbrook
  - Fallbrook (Box 5)
- Floods
  - Floods (Box 5)
- Forest Lawn (Glendale)
  - Forest Lawn (Glendale) (Box 5)
- Fresno
  - Fresno (Box 20)
- Gardena
  - Gardena (Box 5)
- Garvanza
  - Garvanza (Box 5)
- Getting to California
  - Getting to California (Box 5)
- Glendale
  - Glendale (Box 5)
- Glendora
  - Glendora (Box 5)
- Greetings from
  - Greetings from: California,Southern California, Los Angeles (Box 10)
- Hemet
  - Hemet (Box 10)
- Hermosa Beach
  - Hermosa Beach (Box 10)
- Highland
  - Highland (Box 10)
- Highland Park
  - Highland Park (Box 10)
- Highways
  - Highways: See also: Coast Highway, Plank Road, Ridge Route (Box 10)
- Hollywood
  - Hollywood (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Arthur Letts' Home (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Bernheimer Japanese Gardens (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Cahuenga Pass (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Castle Sans Souci (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Churches (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Grauman's Chinese Theatre (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Grauman's Egyptian Theatre (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Hollywood Bowl (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Hotels - Hotel Hollywood (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Hotels - Roosevelt Hotel (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Hotels & apartment buildings (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Laurel Canyon / Lookout Mountain (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Paul DeLongpre home (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Restaurants & clubs (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Streets (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Studios (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Theatres (Box 18)
  - Hollywood: Wattle's gardens (Box 18)
- Huntington Park
  - Huntington Park (Box 10)
- Idyllwild
  - Idyllwild (Box 10)
- Imperial Valley
  - Imperial Valley (Box 10)
- Indio
  - Indio (Box 10)
- Inglewood
  - Inglewood (Box 10)
- Irrigation
  - Irrigation (Box 10)
- Knott's Berry Farm
  - Knott's Berry Farm (Box 10)
  - Knott's Berry Farm (Box 20)
- La Jolla
  - La Jolla (Box 10)
- Laguna
  - Laguna (Box 10)
  - Laguna (Box 22)
- Lake Elsinore
  - Lake Elsinore (Box 10)
- Lakewood
  - Lakewood (Box 10)
- Loma Linda
  - Loma Linda (Box 10)
- Long Beach
  - Long Beach (Box 10)
  - Long Beach (Box 20)
  - Long Beach (Box 22)
  - Long Beach: Auditorium (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Bath House (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Churches (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: City (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Earthquake 1933 (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Hotels (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Parks (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Residences (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Sanitarium (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Schools (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: Signal Hill (Box 10)
  - Long Beach: YMCA (Box 10)
- Los Angeles
  - Los Angeles: Adams / West Adams (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles: Alligator Farm (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles: Angel's Flight (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles: Apartment buildings (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Aqueduct (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Architecture (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Birdseye views - Los Angeles city (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Botanic Garden (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Brentwood Park / Grand Ave. (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Broadway (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Buildings (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Bungalows (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Businesses (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Caliente Golf Course (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Central Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Central Park (Box 22)
  - Los Angeles: Chester Place (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Chinatown (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Churches (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Chutes Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: City Hall (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: City Hall (old) (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: County Fair (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Court House / Hall of Records (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Crossroads of the World (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Downtown (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: East Side Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Eastlake Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Eastlake Park (Box 22)
  - Los Angeles: Echo Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Elysian Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Exposition Park (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Farmers' Market (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Fiesta de Los Angeles / Fiesta de Las Flores (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Figueroa St. (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Fire Department (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Freeways (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: General views (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: General views (Box 20)
  - Los Angeles: Grider's Birdland (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles: Griffith Park / Observatory / Greek Theater (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hollenbeck home (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hollenbeck Park (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hospitals (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Alexandria (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Ambassador (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Angelus (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Biltmore (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Bimini Hot Springs (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Hollenbeck (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Lankershim (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - New Rosslyn (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Van Nuys (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Hotels - Westminster (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: La Brea Tar Pits (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Lafayette Park (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Larchmont / Third St. (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Lincoln Park (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Little Tokyo (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Los Angeles Museum (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Los Angeles River (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Mission Village (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Motels (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Movie industry - studios, sets, etc. (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Oil wells (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Olvera Street (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Olympics 1932 (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Ostrich Farm (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Otis residence (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Palmetto Ave. (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Park La Brea (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Pershing Square (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Pershing Square (Box 22)
  - Los Angeles: Pigeon Farm (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Port Los Angeles (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Produce Market (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Public Library (Box 22)
  - Los Angeles: Radium Sulphur Springs (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Railroad stations & trains (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Residences (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Restaurants (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Saint James Park (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Schools (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Selig Zoo (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: South Park (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Southwest Museum (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Spring St. (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles: Stars' homes (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Stars' homes (Box 20)
  - Los Angeles: Sunset Blvd. (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Theatres (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Union Station (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Victory Service Club (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Watts Towers (Box 20)
  - Los Angeles: Westlake / MacArthur Park (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Westlake Park (Box 22)
  - Los Angeles: Wild Animal Farm (California Wild Animal Farm) (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Wilshire Blvd. (Box 13)
  - Los Angeles: Windsor Square (Box 13)
- Los Angeles Times
  - Los Angeles Times (Box 22)
- Malibu
  - Malibu (Box 13)
- Mammoth Lake
  - Mammoth Lake (Box 13)
- Manhattan Beach
  - Manhattan Beach (Box 13)
- Maps
  - Maps (Box 13)
- Mare Island
  - Mare Island (Box 13)
- Matilija Canyon
  - Matilija Canyon: Ventura County (Box 13)
- Merced River
  - Merced River (Box 22)
- Miller, Joaquin
  - Miller, Joaquin (Box 22)
- Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous - Union Oil cards & Northern California: [box not full] (Box 2)
- Missions
  - Missions (Box 13)
  - Missions: La Purisima Concepcion (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Antonio de Pala (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Buenaventura (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Diego de Alcala (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Fernando Rey (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Gabriel (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Juan Capistrano (Box 13)
  - Missions: San Luis Rey (Box 13)
  - Missions: Santa Barbara (Box 13)
  - Missions: Santa Ynez (Box 13)
- Modjeska homes
  - Modjeska homes (Box 13)
- Mojave
  - Mojave (Box 13)
- Mono County
  - Mono County (Box 13)
- Monrovia
  - Monrovia (Box 13)
  - Monrovia (Box 20)
- Montrose
  - Montrose (Box 13)
- Mount Baldy
  - Mount Baldy (Box 13)
- Mount Hamilton
  - Mount Hamilton (Box 13)
- Mount Lowe
  - Mount Lowe (Box 13)
- Mount Rubidoux
  - Mount Rubidoux (Box 14)
- Mount San Bernardino
  - Mount San Bernardino (Box 14)
- Mount San Gorgonio
  - Mount San Gorgonio (Box 14)
- Mount San Jacinto
  - Mount San Jacinto (Box 14)
- Mount Washington (Los Angeles)
  - Mount Washington (Los Angeles) (Box 14)
- Mount Wilson
  - Mount Wilson (Box 14)
- Murrieta Hot Springs
  - Murrieta Hot Springs (Box 14)
- Naples (Long Beach)
  - Naples (Long Beach) (Box 14)
- Native Americans
  - Native Americans (Box 14)
- Needles
  - Needles (Box 14)
- Newport Beach
  - Newport Beach (Box 14)
- Northern California
  - Northern California (Box 1)
  - Northern California (Box 3)
  - Northern California (except San Francisco): Includes Yosemite (Box 6)
  - Northern California (no San Francisco): [box not full] (Box 8)
- Ocean Park (Santa Monica)
  - Ocean Park (Santa Monica) (Box 14)
- Oceanside
  - Oceanside (Box 14)
- Oil wells
  - Oil wells (Box 14)
- Ojai
  - Ojai (Box 14)
- Ontario
  - Ontario (Box 14)
- Orange & Orange County
  - Orange & Orange County (Box 14)
- Owens Valley
  - Owens Valley (Box 14)
- Oxnard
  - Oxnard (Box 14)
- Pacific Palisades
  - Pacific Palisades (Box 14)
- Palm Desert
  - Palm Desert (Box 14)
- Palm Springs
  - Palm Springs: General views (Box 14)
  - Palm Springs: Hotels - Deep Well Guest Ranch (Box 14)
  - Palm Springs: Hotels - Desert Inn (Box 14)
  - Palm Springs: Hotels - El Mirador (Box 14)
  - Palm Springs: Hotels - Palm Springs Hotel (Box 14)
  - Palm Springs: Hotels, motels, apartments (Box 14)
- Palmdale
  - Palmdale (Box 14)
- Palomar Observatory
  - Palomar Observatory (Box 14)
- Palos Verdes
  - Palos Verdes (Box 14)
- Pasadena
  - Pasadena: Apartments (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Arroyo Seco (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Brookside Park (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Bungalows (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Busch Gardens (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Cawston's Ostrich Farm (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Central Park (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Churches (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: City Hall (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Colorado St. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Community Playhouse (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Eaton Canyon (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Fair Oaks Ave. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Foothill Blvd. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: General views (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: General views (Box 20)
  - Pasadena: Hospitals (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels - Hotel Green (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels - Hotel Maryland (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels - Hotel Raymond (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels - Hotel Wentworth (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Hotels - Huntington Hotel (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Huntington Library (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Library (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Los Robles Ave. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Marengo Ave. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Oneonta Park (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Orange Grove Ave. (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Residences - Robert J. Burdette home (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Residences / Gardens (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Salt Lake Depot (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Schools (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Throop Institute (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Tournament of Roses / Rose Bowl (Box 19)
  - Pasadena: Tournament of Roses 1928, 1929, 1940, 1941 (Box 20)
  - Pasadena: Williams Park (Box 19)
- Pine Crest
  - Pine Crest (Box 14)
- Plank Road (Highway 80)
  - Plank Road (Highway 80) (Box 14)
- Plants
  - Plants: Bouganvillea (Box 14)
  - Plants: Desert (Box 14)
  - Plants: Garden scenes (Box 14)
  - Plants: General (Box 14)
  - Plants: Hydrangeas (Box 14)
  - Plants: Oranges (Box 14)
  - Plants: Oranges (Box 20)
  - Plants: Palms (Box 14)
  - Plants: Pampas grass (Box 14)
  - Plants: Poinsettias (Box 14)
  - Plants: Poppies (Box 14)
  - Plants: Roses (Box 14)
  - Plants: Wildflowers (Box 14)
  - Plants: Wisteria (Box 14)
- Playa del Rey
  - Playa del Rey (Box 15)
- Pomona
  - Pomona (Box 15)
- Ramona legend
  - Ramona legend (Box 15)
  - Ramona legend (Box 22)
  - Ramona legend: Ramona's Marriage Place [San Diego] (Box 20)
- Rancho Santa Fe
  - Rancho Santa Fe (Box 15)
- Redlands
  - Redlands (Box 15)
  - Redlands (Box 22)
  - Redlands: Residences (Box 15)
  - Redlands: Residences - A.K. Smiley (Box 15)
- Redondo Beach
  - Redondo Beach (Box 15)
- Redwood Highway
  - Redwood Highway (Box 20)
- Richardson Springs
  - Richardson Springs (Box 15)
- Ridge Route
  - Ridge Route (Box 15)
- Riverside
  - Riverside (Box 15)
  - Riverside (Box 20)
  - Riverside (Box 22)
  - Riverside: County Court House (Box 22)
  - Riverside: General views (Box 15)
  - Riverside: Magnolia Avenue (Box 22)
  - Riverside: Mission Inn (Box 15)
  - Riverside: Sherman Institute (Box 15)
- Rubio Canyon
  - Rubio Canyon (Box 15)
- Salton Sea
  - Salton Sea (Box 15)
- San Bernardino
  - San Bernardino (Box 15)
  - San Bernardino (Box 22)
- San Bernardino Mountains
  - San Bernardino Mountains (Box 15)
- San Clemente
  - San Clemente (Box 15)
- San Diego
  - San Diego (Box 22)
  - San Diego: America's Exposition 1935 (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Balboa Park (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Balboa Park (Box 22)
  - San Diego: Bennington Monument (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Bentley Ostrich Farm (Box 15)
  - San Diego: California Pacific International Exposition - 1935 (Box 22)
  - San Diego: California Pacific International Exposition 1935 (Box 15)
  - San Diego: General views (Box 15)
  - San Diego: General views (Box 20)
  - San Diego: Hotels (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Hotels (Box 22)
  - San Diego: Mission Cliff Park (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Old Town (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Old Town (Box 22)
  - San Diego: Panama - California Exposition 1915 (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Panama - California Exposition 1915 (Box 20)
  - San Diego: Point Loma (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Residences (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Schools (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Sunset Cliffs (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Sweetwater Dam (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Theosophical Society (Box 15)
  - San Diego: Zoo (Box 15)
- San Fernando Valley
  - San Fernando Valley (Box 15)
- San Francisco
  - San Francisco (Box 9)
  - San Francisco: Panama -Pacific International Expo 1915 (Box 20)
  - San Francisco, including 1906 fire (Box 4)
- San Gabriel
  - San Gabriel (Box 16)
  - San Gabriel: Mission Play (Box 16)
- San Jacinto
  - San Jacinto (Box 16)
- San Juan Capistrano
  - San Juan Capistrano (Box 16)
- San Onofre
  - San Onofre (Box 16)
- San Pedro
  - San Pedro (Box 16)
- Santa Ana, Calif.
  - Santa Ana, Calif. (Box 16)
- Santa Anita
  - Santa Anita (Box 16)
- Santa Barbara
  - Santa Barbara: Castle Rock (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Court House (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: De La Guerra House (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Earthquake, 1925 (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Fiesta (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Gardens (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: General views (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - Arlington Hotel (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - Biltmore (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - El Encanto (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - El Mirador (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - Potter (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels - Samarkand (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Hotels and motels (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Los Banos Del Mar (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Miramar (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Railroad stations (Box 16)
  - Santa Barbara: Saint Anthony's College (Box 16)
- Santa Barbara - El Paseo
  - Santa Barbara - El Paseo (Box 16)
- Santa Barbara - Residences
  - Santa Barbara - Residences (Box 16)
- Santa Catalina Island
  - Santa Catalina Island (Box 16)
  - Santa Catalina Island: Hotels (Box 17)
  - Santa Catalina Island: Residences (Box 17)
  - Santa Catalina Island, cont. (Box 17)
- Santa Fe Springs
  - Santa Fe Springs (Box 17)
- Santa Maria
  - Santa Maria (Box 17)
- Santa Monica
  - Santa Monica: Longest Wharf in the World SEE ALSO: Los Angeles - Port Los Angeles (Box 17)
  - Santa Monica: See also: Ocean Park (Box 17)
- Santa Monica Canyon
  - Santa Monica Canyon (Box 17)
- Santa Paula
  - Santa Paula (Box 17)
- Sherman Oaks
  - Sherman Oaks (Box 17)
- Ships
  - Ships (Box 17)
- Sierra Madre
  - Sierra Madre (Box 17)
- Soldier's Home (West Los Angeles)
  - Soldier's Home (West Los Angeles) (Box 17)
- Solvang
  - Solvang (Box 17)
- Southern California
  - Southern California (Box 20)
  - Southern California: "California Dreamin" album, incl. LA, Pasadena, Hollywood, Palm Springs, etc. (Box 20)
  - Southern California: General (Box 17)
- Summerland
  - Summerland (Box 17)
- Tarzana
  - Tarzana (Box 17)
- Tehachapi
  - Tehachapi (Box 17)
- Thermal
  - Thermal (Box 17)
- Thousand Oaks
  - Thousand Oaks (Box 17)
- Topanga Canyon
  - Topanga Canyon (Box 17)
- Torrance
  - Torrance (Box 17)
- Twentynine Palms
  - Twentynine Palms (Box 17)
- U.S. - Mexican border
  - U.S. - Mexican border (Box 22)
- Upland
  - Upland (Box 17)
- Van Nuys / Lankershim
  - Van Nuys / Lankershim (Box 17)
- Venice
  - Venice (Box 17)
  - Venice (Box 22)
- Ventura County
  - Ventura County (Box 17)
  - Ventura County (Box 22)
- Victorville
  - Victorville (Box 17)
- Vidal
  - Vidal (Box 17)
- Westwood
  - Westwood (Box 17)
- Whittier
  - Whittier (Box 17)
- Wilmington
  - Wilmington (Box 17)